De la Torre Family Papers, 1874-2003 (bulk: 1910-1946)
Special Collections at the University of Arizona Libraries
- Oversize Materials. 1906-1979
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - De la Torre Berumen Family. undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - De la Torre Family. undated, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - Franciscan Priests and Friends. undated, 1921-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - General. undated, 1909-1932 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - Grupos de Tampico, Tamaulipas. undated, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and Negatives: Photographs - Velasco de Garibi Family. undated, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Oversize: Photographs—Ruiz de Chavez Family 1912 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Oversize: Photographs—Asociación Católica de la Juventud Mexicana 1920 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Addition of Manuscripts and Family Photographs, 1910-2003
  This series contains an addition of materials collected by Jose De la Torre. The series is divided in subseries that mirror the arrangement of the original collection. Subseries include biographical files, correspondence, subject files, printed materials, photographs, and oversized materials. Materials are in Spanish.
  - Biographical Files: Miscellaneous, 1939-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre, Alfonso, 1935-1945 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre, Carlos, 1956-1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre, Ignacio, 1953-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre, Ignacio, 1979-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre, Luis, 1910-1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Files: De la Torre Luis and Carmela, 1942-1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1927-2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Alfonso, 1925-1932 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Benjamín, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Carlos, 1932-1953 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Francisco, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Ignacio, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Luis, 1929-1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, María, 1942-1946 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: De la Torre, Robert, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Navarrete, Juan, 1942-1954 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Paloma y Vizcarra, Miguel, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Ruiz de Chávez, Ignacio, 1942-1947 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Subject Files: Miscellanous, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files: Cristero story, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files: Conference Notes and Reflection, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files: Congreso Eucarístico Nacional de México, 1924-1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files: Diary, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files: Liga Nacional Defensora de la Libertad, 1934-1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files: Notes, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files: Prose, undated, 1926-1928 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Miscellaneous, 1924-1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Las Chabelitas, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Album del Primer Congreso Diocesano de Sonora, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Sermon IV Carta Pastoral, 1932-1935 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: Newspaper El Debate, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Religious Publications, 1924-1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Blue Scrapbook, 1927-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: De la Torre, Alfonso, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: De la Torre Family, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: De la Torre Luis and Family, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: De la Torre Uribarren Family – CD, 1921-1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: McGucken, Joseph T., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Ruiz de Chavez, Felipe, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)